Kyle Owen Ga

gakyleowen@gmail.com (+63) 939-119-2839 DECA HOMES Cabantian Davao City, Davao Region

Summary

An ambitious software engineer with three years of experience in Javascript, Typescript, React.js, Vue.js, Express.js, C#, .Net, MongoDB, Postgresql, Graphql API, and REST API. Constant learner and ability to adapt to new technologies. Possess strong communication and team management skills.

Education

Information Technology

AMA Computer College • Davao City, Davao Region 2019–2022 **Dean's Lister**

08/2022

Skills

JavaScript, Typescript, React.js, Next.js, Express.js, Vue.js, C# .Net , Shopify,

Hubspot, MongoDB, Postgre, Mysql, Git, GitHub

Experience

Developer Lead

Hill&Foster Web Design and Branding agency

05/2022 -11/2024

Implementing and creating impactful designs as the lead frontend developer

Developer II

Web-based Fire Safety Inspection Certification System of Bureau of Fire Protection (Davao City)

02/2022 - 05/2022

· Built the front-end for the Certification System for Applicants and Bureau of Fire Protection Employees

Developer II

FWD Springboard Student Challenge • Davao City, Davao Region

09/2021 - 11/2021

- Won Top 3 in the National Level
- · Developed a social media mobile application (with React Native) that allows easy access to insurance globally